dealgrocer.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy | Deal Grocer

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Deal Grocer website (collectively, the “Website” located at www.dealgrocer.com). 

Deal Grocer, Ltd., a Hong Kong corporation, the provider of the Website (referred to as “Deal Grocer”, “us” or “we”), is committed to protecting your privacy online. 

**Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the “User”) and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us.**

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.**

**BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.**

#####  Sections 

#####  Changes to Privacy Policy 

Deal Grocer reserves the right at all times to discontinue or modify this Privacy Policy as we deem necessary or desirable. 

A prominent announcement above the text of this Privacy Policy, as appropriate, will be displayed for thirty (30) days, with such being deemed sufficient notification of such changes. Any such modifications become effective immediately upon being posted to the Site. 

It is your sole responsibility to check the Site from time to time to view any such changes. If you do not agree to any changes, if and when such changes may be made, you must cease use of the Site. Your use of the Site after any modifications to the Privacy Policy indicates that you agree to such modified Privacy Policy. 

Any changes to this Privacy Policy (other than as set forth in this paragraph) or waiver of Deal Grocer's rights hereunder shall not be valid or effective except in a written agreement bearing the physical signature of Deal Grocer's Managing Director. No purported waiver or modification of this Privacy Policy by Deal Grocer via telephonic or email communications shall be valid. 

Should you wish to terminate your account due to a modification to this Privacy Policy, you may do so by sending an email with the subject line "Termination" to the following email address: [team@dealgrocer.com](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com)

#####  Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information 

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: 

  * Personally Identifiable Information and 
  * Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

######  Personally Identifiable Information. 

Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific User. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as, but not limited to, creating an account, ordering Coupons from us, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, entering a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by us or our partners, filling out a survey, posting a review, sending us or our partners feedback, requesting information about our services, submitting an agreement, applying for a job, posting a video or signing up for special offers through the Website (collectively, “Identification Activities”), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. 

If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, telephone number, mobile number, date of birth, gender, personal preferences, and purchase history. When you order a Coupon, we may also ask you to provide us with your credit card number, expiration date, billing address and authentication codes or related information. 

Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity. 

We use Personally Identifiable Information to create your personal Deal Grocer account, provide Coupons to you, administer sweepstakes and contests, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with us and third parties as provided in Item 3 of this Privacy Policy. 

Specifically, we may use personal preferences which you provide us to serve targeted offers to you, or if you send our customer service an email we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. 

When creating your account, you may decide to enroll in our regular email alert service to receive our Promotional Emails as described in Item 6 of this Privacy Policy. You may also subscribe to our Promotional Emails without creating an account with us. We will use your email address to send you Promotional Emails with regular updates on our offerings and services. You may decide to unsubscribe from our Promotional Emails at any time by following the instructions provided in Item 6 of this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, if you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. 

######  Tell-A-Friend. 

If you choose to use our referral service, we may ask you for your friend's first and last name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. Deal Grocer stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

######  Gifting. 

If you choose to buy a Coupon for a friend, we may ask you for your friend's first and last name, date of birth, home or office address, and email address. We will automatically send your friend an email with the gift you bought for them, or the gift may also be sent by post. Deal Grocer stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this email, and sending their gift. Your friend may contact us at [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

######  Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific User. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags. 

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming. 

#####  Release of Personally Identifiable Information 

We will not share, sell, rent, or trade your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below: 

######  We may share your information with Deal Grocer Merchants. 

From time to time, we offer Coupons for sale which may be exchanged for products/services with particular merchants (referred to as “Deal Grocer Merchants”) who are provided with information on Deal Grocer customers who purchased the Coupon in order to aid redemption. In those cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with Deal Grocer Merchants. Sharing this Information may allow a Deal Grocer Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a Deal Grocer Merchant if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the Deal Grocer Merchant involved in that Identification Activity. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such Deal Grocer Merchant. 

######  We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers. 

We provide services and products through third parties. These “Third Party Service Providers” perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. 

We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies (“Affiliates”), such as Deal Grocer Merchants, with whom we have business relationships and may share your information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. For example, when you order a Coupon, we release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the service and, if applicable, release your address to the delivery service to deliver the service. Likewise, we may release an Affiliate's information to our bank to send out a payment. 

We encourage Deal Grocer Merchants and Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. 

However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. 

######  We may remarket your information. 

Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with the Deal Grocer website. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by Deal Grocer to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, may show Deal Grocer ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Deal Grocer's website. This information is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose. 

######  We may share your information in a Business Transfer. 

As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

######  We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others. 

#####  Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We may disclose, share, rent, or sell Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with “Third Party Advertisers” or “Third Party Advertising Companies” and other parties as provided below. 

We may use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

We may also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us. 

We may also aggregate all survey responses and anonymize the data and make such available to affiliates and other third parties. 

#####  Updating and Correcting Information 

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by logging into your account and accessing the "settings" section of the site, sending us an email at [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com) or writing to us 4304 43F China Resources Bldg. 26 Harbour Road, Wanchai, Hong Kong. Please indicate your name, address and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us. 

We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Website. In addition, in may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information because we periodically backup information. 

Should you wish to terminate your account for any reason, you may do so by sending an email with the subject line "Termination" to the following email address: [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com)

#####  User Choices on Collection and Use of Information 

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in a certain activity on the Website. 

As a condition of purchase of our Coupons, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will send you information regarding your account activity and purchases as well as updates about our products and promotional offers. 

You cannot opt-out of Administrative Emails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User's activity on the Website, and include emails regarding a particular User's account, requests or inquiries, and purchases of Coupons. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have a choice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise our Coupons and services, including exclusive sales and other offers, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you may elect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registering by emailing us at [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com) or by writing to us at the address contained herein, or by hitting the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of any of our emails, or by changing your account settings. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Promotional Emails you do not want to receive. 

#####  Security of Information 

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information (such as credit card information) using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information. 

#####  Data Tracking 

######  Cookies. 

To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. 

In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly. 

######  Other Tracking Devices. 

We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. 

Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes. 

#####  Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites 

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on www.dealgrocer.com. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you review the website's privacy policy. The ability to access information of third-parties from Deal Grocer, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their products, their services, other websites, locations or their content. 

If you choose to access a third party Site linked to our Site, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third party Sites. We are not responsible for how these other companies or organizations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide them. 

#####  Miscellaneous Privacy Issues 

######  Children. 

Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use the Website and we do not intentionally collect or maintain personal information from those who are under 13 years old. If we obtain information that a user is under 13, or that a user has misrepresented his/her age and is actually below 13, we will take steps to remove that user's personal information permanently from our databases. We recommend that children between the ages of 13 and 18 obtain their parent's permission before submitting information over the internet. 

By using the Website, you are representing that you are at least 18 years old, or that you are at least 13 years old and have a parent's or guardian's permission to use the Website. 

Some Coupons may be subject to further age limitations. 

######  Public Areas. 

We may provide areas on our Website where you can publicly post information about yourself, can communicate with others such as discussion boards or blogs, or can review products, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may be accessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites or web searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and used by others. 

For example, if you post your email address along with a public restaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. The username and photo you provide for your Deal Grocer account may be seen by the public when you make any comments or ask any question on publicly viewable sections of the Site. We have no control over who reads your postings or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information. 

######  Facebook Connect. 

The Deal Grocer Website may allow users to access Facebook Connect to interact with friends and to share on Facebook through Wall and friends' News Feeds. If you are logged into Deal Grocer and Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" your profiles will merge if the email addresses match. If the email addresses don't match, we ask you if you want to merge them and you must enter your Deal Grocer password to validate that they control that account. If you are already logged into Deal Grocer but not logged into Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" you will be prompted to enter your Facebook credentials or to "Sign up for Facebook." By proceeding you are allowing the Deal Grocer Website to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of Deal Grocer Sites. Conversely, if you are not currently registered as a Deal Grocer user and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook," you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join Deal Grocer. Once you register on the Deal Grocer Website and Connect with Facebook, you will be able to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook. You have the option to disable Facebook Connect at any time by logging into "My Profile" and clicking on "My Facebook Profile." Further, you can edit privacy settings for the reviews that appear on Facebook or disconnect this service by visiting the Facebook Application Settings page. 

#####  Contacting Us 

Whether you're a new or loyal customer, restaurant owner, hotel owner, business owner, marketer, publisher, media member or job seeker we'd like to stay connected and want to hear from you! Contact us at [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com)

######  Corporate Address 

Deal Grocer, Ltd.   
4304 43F China Resources Bldg.   
26 Harbour Road, Wanchai, Hong Kong 

Service Inquiries [ team@dealgrocer.com ](mailto:team@dealgrocer.com)
